早上好
Good morning.
来 瞧瞧
Tch-tch-tch. Oh, here, look at that.
嘘
Shh.
你能开门吗
Could you open the gate?
尤金
Eugene.
怎么了
Yeah?
开门
Open the gate.
我们出去看看能不能找到一些物资
Goin' out to see if we can find anything.
等他们来时给他们
for when they come.
想帮忙吗
You want to help?
我认为我无法胜任
I don't believe I'd be up to that.
听起来一点不奇怪
Yeah, sounds about right.
我在为他们修这个便携式音频系统
I'm repairin' this portable audio system for them.
他们来时 我们会有一个很体面的
We'll have a perfectly respectable music player.
音乐播放器
when they arrive.
我在做有把握的事
I'm dealing in certainties,
在尽力提供他们想要的东西
and I'm doing my part to give them what they want.
∮ 当 当 当 当 ∮
∮ Dun-dun-dun dun ∮
小猪 小猪 让我进去
Little pig, little pig, let me in!
怎么
Well?
你是哪位
Um, who are you?
你最好是在开玩笑
Oh, you better be jokin'.
尼根 露西尔
Negan, Lucille.
我知道我得留下深刻的第一印象
I know I had to make a pretty strong first impression.
你好啊
Well, hello, there.
别逼我开口问
Do not make me have to ask.
你说的是一周
You said a week.
你来早了
You're early.
我想你了
I missed you.
瑞克 过来
Oh, Rick, come on out here.
瞧瞧
Watch this.
归我了
Calling it!
真是轻而易举
Easy peasy lemon squeezy!
好了 各位
All right, everybody.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
大日子啊
Big day.
瑞克 你看见我刚做的事了吗
Hey, Rick, you see that, what I just did?
那是上好服务
That is some service!
我们差点被拒之门外了
I mean, we almost get turned away at the gate.
那人是谁啊
"Who is that guy, anyway?"
我生气了吗 发脾气了吗
Do I get mad? Do I throw a fit?
我砸了哪个红毛的头吗
Do I bash some ginger's dome in?
没有
Nope.
我只是干掉了一个
I just take care of one of these dead pricks.
可能杀死你们的行尸
that could've killed one of y'all.
服务
Service.
拿着
Hold this.
《行尸走肉》
天啊
Hot diggity dog!
这地方真是了不起
This place is magnificent!
如俗话说 富得流油
An embarrassment of riches, as they say.
先生 我相信你们肯定有许多
Yes, sir, I do believe you are gonna have plenty.
可提供的东西
to offer up.
达里尔
Daryl, hey …
不
No.
Nope.
他是帮手
He's the help.
你不准看他
You don't look at him,
不准跟他说话
you don't talk to him,
否则我要你砍掉他身体的某个部位
and I don't make you chop anything off of him.
大家都一样
Same goes for everyone.
对吧
Right?
刚才悬念很多啊
A lot of suspense there.
她都不知道有多少
I don't think she even knew how much.
好了 开始行动吧
All right, let's get this show on the road.
看看你们橱柜里有什么好东西
See what kind of goodies you got in the cupboard.
我们分好了一半补给
We put aside half the supplies.
不 瑞克
No, Rick.
不
No.
你无权决定我们拿走什么
You don't decide what we take.
我来决定
I do.
阿拉特
Arat.
你们听到老大的话了
You heard the man.
出发
Move out!
他们就搜一搜房子
They're just gonna search the houses a bit,
继续搜刮
keep the process movin'.
好
All right.
你要带我在这里转转吗
You gonna show me around or not?
怎么样
Well?
罗西塔
Rosita!
你跟你的朋友去哪里
Where you going with your friend here?
我们打算去…
We were just heading back to …
知道吗 我不在乎
You know what? I don't care.
这些事搞定了
Now that that's all settled,
我有份工作给你做
I got a job for ya.
把达里尔的摩托弄过来
Go get me Daryl's bike.
不在这里
It ain't here.
如果不在这里
Well, if it ain't here,
那你知道它在哪里吧
then you know where it is, right?
我俩都清楚你是知道的
We both know you know where it is.
现在你可以走了
Now you're good to go.
走吧
So go.
别花太长时间
Don't take too long.
该死的
Damn it.
瞧见了吗
You see this?
这种场景让我满意极了
This is the kind of thing that just tickles my balls.
一点点合作
A little cooperation.
让一切都特别舒心
and everything is pleasant as punch.
你瞧 一旦你们了解了我们
You see, we really are reasonable people.
就会发现我们真的特别讲道理
once you get to know us.
很诚信
Honest.
爽
Man.
- 靠 我真爱这地方 - 尼根
- Damn, I love this place! - Negan.
你可能会想看看这玩意
Somethin' you might wanna see.
我瞧瞧这是什么
What do we have here?
我希望是什么变态小视频
I got my fingers crossed for a little freaky-deaky.
…了解我
…know me.
我杀过人
I've killed people.
- 数都数不清 - 老天爷
- I don't even know how many by now. - Jee-hee-sus!
但是我知道为什么他们都死了
But I know why they're all dead.
那是你吗 瑞克
Is that you, Rick,
- 那张胡子拉碴的脸 - 只有他们死了 我的家人
- underneath all that man-bush? - They're dead so my family,
- 和外面那些人才能活下去 - 我靠
- all those people out there, can be alive. - Shee-ot.
我可不敢惹那个人
I would not have messed with that guy.
但你已经不是那个人了
But that's not you anymore…
是吧
is it?
没错
Nope.
我真得刮刮胡子了
I really gotta shave this shit.
那个生病的姑娘怎么样了
Whatever happened to that sick girl?
那晚对她而言压力可大了
That seemed like a hell of a stressful night for her.
她当时那哭闹的样子
The way she was carrying on,
看来她是二号的老婆 是吧
she was married to number two, right?
注意点
Careful.
注意自己看我的眼神 瑞克
Careful how you're lookin' at me, Rick.
寡妇 特别是那些长成她那样的…
Widows, especially ones that look like that…
她们…很特别
they…are special.
我爱她们
I love 'em.
她们的丈夫去世之后 她们…
Right after their husbands go, they are just…
身边就没人了
empty side.
不过这种情况不会持续太久
But usually not for long.
她在哪里
Where is she?
我想见见她
I would love to see her.
你想去祭奠她吗
Do you care to pay your respects?
我靠
Ho-ly crap!
你太他妈渗人了
You are creepy as shit,
悄悄摸摸地靠近我
sneaking up on me,
戴着罗马领 脸上挂着诡异的微笑
wearin' that collar with that freaky-ass smile.
抱歉
My apologies.
我是加百利神父
I'm Father Gabriel.
她没挺过来吗
She didn't make it?
真是悲剧
Damn tragedy.
这就是场悲剧
That's what this is.
你们一定很难过吧
Well, this must really suck for you guys.
一号的死
Number one?
那算在我头上 我当时别无选择
That was on me. No choice there.
必须给你们个教训
Lessons had to be learned.
但是二号
But number two?
他不是必须得死的
That didn't need to happen.
达里尔 是他逼我的
Daryl, there, he forced my hand.
那大概把她压垮了吧
Probably put her right on her back, huh?
该死
Damn.
我本来打算让她和我一起回去的
I was gonna ask her to come back with me.
我知道你在想什么
Oh, I know what you're thinkin'.
我怎么可能赢得她的芳心呢
How could I have a shot,
我这个把她丈夫的头打碎了的人
guy that just bashed her husband's head in?
你绝对想不到的
You'd be surprised.
人啊 他们…
Boy, people, they …
放一些回去 不然下一颗就打你身上了
Put some back or the next one goes in you.
小子…
Kid…
你觉得接下来会发生什么
what do you think happens next?
你会死
You die.
卡尔 卡尔 把枪放下
Carl, Carl, put it down.
不行 他拿走了我们所有的药品
No. He's taking all of our medicine.
他们说了只拿一半的
They said only half our stuff.
当然
Of course.
真要这样吗 小子
Really, kid?
你们该走了
And you should go.
趁你们还没领教到我们是多危险的人之前
Before you find out how dangerous we all are.
你说什么 年轻人
Well, pardon me, young man.
不好意思我他妈爆粗了 但是…
Excuse the shit out of my goddamn French, but…
你刚是威胁了我吗
did you just threaten me?
听着 我理解你为什么威胁戴维
Look, I get threatening Davey here,
但我不能容忍
but I can't have it.
不能威胁他 不能威胁我
Not him, not me.
- 卡尔 放下枪 - 别无礼 瑞克
- Carl, just put it down. - Don't be rude, Rick.
我们正在谈话呢
We are having a conversation here.
孩子 我们说到哪了
Now, boy, where were we?
对了
Oh, yeah.
你真是胆大包天
Your giant, man-sized balls.
别威胁我们
No threatening us.
听着 我喜欢你
Listen, I like you,
所以我不想用暴力证明什么
so I don't want to go hard proving a point here.
你不想那样的
You don't want that.
我以前说了一半
I said half your shit,
哪一半是我说了算
and half is what I say it is.
我很认真
I'm serious.
你想让我证明我有多认真吗
Do you want me to prove how serious?
再一次吗
Again?
知道吗瑞克 这一切都在提醒我
You know, Rick, this whole thing reminds me.
你们的枪太多了
that you have a lot of guns.
有你们从我的哨站抢来的一批枪
There's all the guns you took from my outpost.
还有你们用来干掉
when you wasted all my people.
哨站人的一大批自己的武器
with a shit-ton of your own guns,
我敢打赌你们还有更多枪
and I'm bettin' there's even more,
加起来一共…
which adds up to an absolute…
是超他妈多的枪
ass-load of guns,
而这种情绪小爆发
and as this little emotional outburst.
已经明确地证明了…
just made crystal clear…
这我不能允许
I can't allow that.
现在枪都归我了
They're all mine now.
那么告诉我 瑞克
So tell me, Rick…
我的枪在哪
Where are my guns?
我知道你们会来的
I…figured you were coming.
带他去看枪 奥利维亚
Show him where the guns are, Olivia.
武器库在里面
The armory's inside.
你负责管理这里吗
You run the show in here?
我
I…
我只负责记录所有东西 配给口粮 枪支
I just keep track of it all, the rations, the guns.
很好 聪明
Good. Smart.
别让我耽误你
Don't let me stop you.
带她去 小伙子们 看看物资
Take her out, boys. Show 'em the goods.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
在他们忙的同时
While they're at it,
我只想对你说明
I just want to point out to you.
我不会拿一丁点你的食物
that I'm not taking a scrap of your food.
在这里不会多拿
Slim pickin's in here.
而且肯定不只有我注意到了
And I can't be the only one to notice.
你让一个胖女人
that you got a fat lady in charge.
负责管理口粮 对吧
of keeping track of rations, can I?
总之 你们饿死了
Either way, you starve to death,
我就什么也得不到
I don't get shit,
所以目前呢 你可以保留所有食物
so for now, you get to keep all the food.
你看怎么样
How 'bout that?
你想让我说什么
What do you want me to say?
我不知道 瑞克
I don't know, Rick.
道声谢怎么样
How about a thank you.
你觉得不该这样吗
You think that might be in order?
这要求太过分了吗
Or is that too much to ask?!
我知道 我们起了个坏头
I know we started off on the wrong foot,
可我又能说什么呢 是你逼我的 瑞克
but what can I say? You forced my hand, Rick.
但我一直努力想让你明白
But it's like I've been tryin' to tell you…
只要你和我合作 我还是很讲道理的
I'm a very reasonable man as long as you cooperate,
那么我来问你个问题 瑞克
so let me ask you a question, Rick.
你在和我合作吗
Are you cooperating?
这看起来像什么
What's it look like?
我知道这看起来像什么
I know what it looks like.
但我真正想知道的是
But what I really want to know is.
我们能否能在后面找到所有枪支
if we're gonna find all the guns back there.
还是说你私藏了一些 在等待时机
or if maybe you got a few just waitin' for their moment…
就像我的露西尔一样
just like my Lucille.
枪都在这里了 就我所知
They're all in there, to the best of my knowledge.
希望如此 瑞克
I am countin' on that, Rick.
还在
Still here.
听着 我知道这样做很逊 但你也看到局面了
Look, I know this sucks, but you saw what happened.
你看到他们今天来了多少人
You saw how many of them are there today.
就这样了 都结束了
That's it. It's over.
这就是我们的命运
This is our life now.
瑞克把我们带上了这条路
This is where Rick got us.
也许如果瑞克能深思熟虑
Maybe if Rick thought it through,
一切都会不同
it would've been different.
有些人也许还活着
People might still be with us.
我们现在就这样了
This is where we are.
必须学会接受
We just got to learn to live with it.
罗西塔
Rosita!
知道吗 瑞克 今天是个大日子
You know what today is, Rick? Today is a banner day.
真的
Yes, it is.
我认为咱俩的小协议
I think this little arrangement.
一定能行得通
we have is gonna work out just fine.
等等
Hold up.
看看你有没有好好保养我的枪
Let's see if you've been taking care of my guns.
感觉不错
Feels good.
听起来也不错
Sounds good!
我相信露西尔会有点嫉妒
Oh, I do believe Lucille's gettin' a little jealous.
我的天啊
Well, ho-ly smokes!
看看这个
Look at this!
就是你们把蒂米和迪克小队
It was you guys that took out Little Timmy.
干掉的吗
and the Dick Brigade?
天啊 瑞克
Wow, Rick.
最后过把瘾啊
Gettin' in your last licks.
这会让我有不少乐趣
Ooh, man, I'm gonna have some fun with this.
求你了 我不知道…
Please, I-I don't know for …
阿拉特 不要那么粗鲁
Arat, we don't do that.
除非他们罪有应得
unless they do somethin' to deserve it.
是的 我们查了库存单
Yeah, we went through the inventory.
除了武器库里的枪
Guns in the armory,
墙边的枪 还少几把
guns they had around the walls, they're short.
格洛克9和一支点22山猫
Glock 9 and a.22 Bobcat.
是真的吗
Is that true?
我们有人离开了这里
We had some people leave town.
他们可能带着那些枪
Those guns probably went with them.
所以奥利维亚搞砸了她的工作
So Olivia sucks at her job.
你是想说这个吗
Is that what you're sayin'?
不 我没有这么说
No. No, I'm not sayin' that.
库存单应该统计完整 对吧
There should be a full accounting here, right?
不遗巨细
Top to bottom.
- 我说的对吗 - 不
- Am I right? - No.
我是说 对
I mean, yes.
库存单是对的
The inventory is correct.
很好
Good.
但也不好
But not so good, too.
你看 上面记的
You see, what's in here…
却不在里面 少了两把手枪
isn't in there. You're two handguns short.
你知道在哪吗
Do you know where they are?
不知道 我…
No. I…
真令人沮丧 瑞克
That's dappointing, Rick.
我以为我们已经达成共识了
I thought that we had an understanding.
但这事 说明有人有异议
But this … well, this shows that someone's not on board,
这我不能允许
and I can't have that.
我不喜欢杀女人
I don't enjoy killing women.
男人 我想杀多少杀多少
Men … I can waste them all the live long.
但归根结底 亲爱的奥利维亚
But at the end of the day, Olivia, my dear,
- 这是你的责任 - 这个我们可以解决
- this was your responsibility. - Look, we can work this out.
我们当然可以
Oh, yes, we can.
而且现在我正要去解决
And I'm going to … right now.
这是你的工作 而你搞砸了
This was your job, and you screwed up.
记录枪支情况
Keeping track of guns?
那玩意儿
That shit…
事关生死
is life and death.
我想过藏一些枪
I thought about hiding some of the guns.
我以前藏过
I did it before.
我想过可以埋一些在外面
I figured I could bury some out there.
也许我们很多年都不会碰
Maybe we don't touch them for years.
很多年
Years?
没错
Yeah. That's right.
但如果救世军发现了那些枪
But what if the Saviors find those guns?
如果我们带着那些枪遇到他们
What if we run into them when we have those guns on us?
我们中一个就会死
One of us dies.
也许还不止一个 也许会死很多人
Maybe more than that. Maybe a lot more.
不管我们有多少子弹
Doesn't matter how many bullets we have.
都是不够的
It isn't enough.
他们赢了 事实就是如此
They win. It's that black-and-white.
藏枪不是解决方法 再也不是了
Hiding a couple of guns isn't the answer, not anymore.
我们不必心甘情愿
We don't have to like it,
但我们得把枪交给他们
but we need to give them over.
一把格洛克9和一把点22
A Glock 9 and a.22.
那是他们在找的
That's what they're looking for.
在谁那
Who has it?
有人知道在哪
Someone knows where they are.
或者知道在谁那吗
or they know who does.
如果我们找不到 他们就会杀了奥利维亚
If we don't find them, they're gonna kill Olivia.
他们干得出来
They'll do it.
他们为什么关心
Why do they care?
两把枪又不能威胁到他们
Two guns aren't a threat to them.
但那些枪可以保护我们
But those guns could help protect us.
免受外来人的攻击
from whatever else is out there.
枪在你那吗
Do you have 'em?
倒希望在我这
Wish I did.
大部分人当时不在场
Most of you weren't there.
你们不必看着
You didn't have to watch.
但你们现在可以无视他人的死亡
But you can look away now when someone else dies,
或者你们可以帮忙解决这个问题
or you can help solve this.
给他们想要的 我们就能和平地生活
We give them what they want, and we live in peace.
不要
Don't.
现在不是时候
Now is not the time.
是时候了
It is.
假设我们找到了枪
Say we find the guns.
以后我们该怎么摆脱这困境 瑞克
How are we gonna get out of this, Rick?
摆脱不了了
There is no way out of this.
让我来给你们明确说一遍
Let me put this to all of you as clearly as I can.
管事的不再是我了
I'm not in charge anymore.
是尼根
Negan is.
现在 枪在谁那
Now, who has the guns?
不是所有人都来了
Not everyone's here.
罗西塔
Rosita!
你在哪
Where are you?!
罗西塔
Rosita!
你出来就是为了这个吗
So that's why you're out here?
他们杀了丹妮斯
They killed Denise.
这是空的
It's empty.
要是满的呢
So what if it was full?
你能做什么
What could you do with it?
你不懂吗
Don't you get it?
家里那个混蛋收走我们的枪
That asshole back there took our guns.
是因为他要收走我们所有的枪
because he's gonna take all our guns.
怎么
What?
你想怎么做 告诉他们吗
What are you gonna do, tell them?
这不是我们的命运
This is not our life.
没找到
Nothing.
但是
Still.
我只是
I just…
我觉得
I feel like…
我知道会顺利过去的
I know this is going to work out.
怎么过去
How?
我们会找到枪
We'll find the guns.
我们会熬过今天
We'll get through today.
然后找到继续前进的方法
Then we'll find a way to go forward,
如何抗争
how to beat this.
没有办法抗争的
There is no beating this.
有的 总有办法的
Yes, there is, somehow.
我对我们有信心
I have faith in us.
我对你有信心
I have faith in you.
事情会变的
Things change.
你是我的朋友
You're my friend.
我们
It…
并非一直是朋友
wasn't always that way.
米琼恩呢 她有没有可能…
Where's Michonne? Could she possibly have …
她手上没有他们要的东西
She doesn't have anything they're lookin' for.
你挖的那个坟墓 很机智
What you did with the graves, it was quick thinkin'.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很高兴挖一个没人睡的坟墓
It was nice digging a grave I knew would stay empty.
没找到吗
No luck?
我们搜了罗西塔的房子
We searched the house, Rosita's.
什么都没有
There's nothing.
我们现在怎么办
So what do we do now?
枪最有可能藏在这里
If they were anywhere, they'd be here.
斯宾塞干过类似的事
Spencer's done this kind of thing before.
我们继续找
We keep looking.
也许今天会找到
Maybe today works out.
我去看看车库
I'll check the garage.
我再去看看迪安娜的办公室
I'll look in Deanna's office again.
气球吗
Balloons?
你要去派对吗 小姑娘
You going to a party, little girl?
我能留着吗 拜托
Can I keep them, please?
只是
It's just…
让我留下这些吧
Let me keep them.
再说一遍拜托 小姑娘
Say please again, little girl.
拜托
Please.
好 再说一遍
Yeah. One more time.
拜托
Please.
小心点 小姑娘
Be careful, little girl.
他们很快就走了
They'll be gone soon.
你给我带了什么 瑞克
What you got for me, Rick?
瞧瞧这
Well, would you look at that?
该来的还是来了
They were here after all.
真是有意思 一句「我的天 有人会死」
Funny how a little "Holy shit! Somebody's gonna die!"
就能刺激所有人
lights a fire under everybody's ass!
告诉我 瑞克 你们中哪一位
So, tell me, Rick … which one of your fine folks.
差点要了奥利维亚的命
almost cost Olivia the rest of her days?
- 这不重要 - 不 这很重要
- It doesn't matter anymore. - No, it matters.
你得让所有人都同意
See, you need to get everybody on board.
所有人 不然
Everybody. Or…
我们又要回到原点了
we just go right back to square one.
你这地方真不错啊 瑞克
Hell of a place you got here, Rick.
给我点时间
Give me a second.
不行
No.
拜托 你能…
Please, can you just…
给我点时间吗
give me a second?
他让我拿着的
He had me hold it.
步枪给我
I need the rifle.
什么
What?
我知道在包里装着
I know it's in the bag.
我知道你在外面做什么
I know what you're doing out there.
我在外面做什么
What am I doing out there?
你在练枪
You're practicing.
我们得把枪都交出去 所有枪
We have to give up our guns, all of them.
不行
We can't.
如果你把枪藏起来 让他们找到了
If you keep it, and they find it,
有人会死的
someone dies.
我不要失去你 或者卡尔 或者其他任何人
I'm not losing you or Carl or anyone else.
我不要再失去任何人了
I'm not losing anyone else!
我要把枪交给他们 你让我做吗
Now I'm giving it to them. Are you gonna let me?
瞧瞧这个
Look at this!
我以为她去找补给了
I thought she was scavenging.
她其实是去打猎了
She was hunting.
这支枪没入过库 我们一直在防线上用
This one never came inside. We kept it near the line.
看看阿
Look at this.
关系就该这么建起来
This is something to build a relationship on.
做得好 瑞克
Good for you, Rick.
这就是听进去读懂了
This is readin' the room and gettin' the message.
我以前说过 我要再说一次
I've said it before, I'm gonna say it again.
你这个人呢 很特别
You, sir…are special.
现在你知道了我们会守规矩
Now that you know we can follow your rules…
然后呢
Yes?
我想求你留下达里尔
…I'd like to ask you if Daryl can stay.
不可能
Not happenin'.
你知道吗 我也不确定
You know what? I don't know.
也许达里尔可以自己求我
Maybe Daryl can plead his case.
也许他会说动我
Maybe Daryl can sway me.
达里尔
Daryl?
好了 你试过了
Well, you tried.
现在你要做的是
Now what you got to do.
翻过你们的高墙
is get over that tall wall of yours.
在外面加倍努力
and try harder out there.
为我工作
Earn for me.
因为我们很快就会回来的 到那时候
Because we're coming back soon, and when we do,
你最好拿出点能让我们感兴趣的东西
you better have something interesting for us,
否则 露西尔会按她的方式来
or Lucille, she's gonna have her way.
我再提醒你一遍
I want you to hear that again.
如果你没有拿出让我们感兴趣的东西
If you don't have something interesting for us…
有人就要死了
somebody's gonna die.
不要再出现神奇的枪了
And no more magic guns.
阿拉特 带上鹿 天色晚了
Arat, grab that deer. It's getting late.
我们回家
Let's go home.
我就喜欢请我吃饭
Man, I love a gal that buys me dinner.
又不用我费心的姑娘了
and doesn't expect me to put out.
归我了
I'll take that.
罗西塔
Rosita!
给你准备了个小感谢礼物
Got a little thank-you.
这就是你们得到的
That's all you're getting back.
我们拿走了全部的枪 大部分床垫
Took all your guns, most of your beds.
希望你美丽的小脑袋能找到地方躺下
I hope you find a place to lay your pretty little head.
在外面找到其他东西了吗
Did you find anything else out there?
只有你死去的朋友们
Just your dead friends.
可以还给你
You can have it back.
只要你说那句话
Just say the word.
今天没人死
So, nobody died.
知道我怎么想的吗
And you know what I think?
我觉得咱俩加强了彼此的理解
I think you and I, we've refined our understanding.
我问问你 瑞克
Let me ask you something, Rick.
想让我走吗
Do you want me to go?
那再好不过了
I think that'd be good.
那就说那两个神奇的字吧
Then just say those two magical words.
谢谢
Thank you.
别搞笑了 应该我谢谢你
Don't be ridiculous. Thank you.
又一个
Another one.
你需要我们的帮助
You need our help.
戴维 把那个烛台给我
Davey, hand me that candlestick over there.
你知道我怎么想的吗 瑞克
You know what I think, Rick?
我觉得我们各取所需 都会是赢家
I think we're both gonna come out of this winners.
看我
Watch my form!
不错
Yep.
双赢
Win-win.
把它洗好等我下次用
You should clean that up for me for next time.
我们走吧
Let's move out!
等等
Oh, wait.
我太粗心了
How careless of me.
你不会以为我要丢下露西尔吧
You didn't think I was gonna leave Lucille, did ya?
她的所作所为之后
I mean, after what she did,
你们怎么会想要她呢
why would you want 'er?
感谢你们这么配合 我的朋友
Thank you for being so accommodating, friend.
以防万一你不明白
In case you haven't caught on…
我刚刚把鸡巴塞进了你的嘴里
I just slipped my dick down your throat,
你还为此感谢了我
and you thanked me for it.
（欢迎来到亚历山大安全区 迷途者的天堂 掠夺者的地狱）
斯宾塞
Spencer.
我们拿走了你屋里的枪
We took the guns you had in your house.
救世军想要我们全部的枪
The Saviors wanted ours, all of them.
库存单上有两把不见了
There were two missing from the inventory.
他们要杀了奥利维亚
They were gonna kill Olivia.
斯宾塞
Spencer.
你进了我屋子
You went into my house?
他们要杀了奥利维亚啊
They were gonna kill Olivia.
听着 我不怪你藏枪
Look, I'm not faulting you for having the guns.
我也干过 但是食品和酒
I did it myself. But the food and liquor?
那是因为你很卑鄙 斯宾塞
That's 'cause you're small, Spencer.
你很脆弱
You're weak.
在墙里算你走运
You got lucky with the walls.
有我们算你走运
You got lucky with us.
我们应该趁有机会的时候和他们谈协议
We should've made a deal with them when we could've.
是啊 我们真走运
Oh, yeah, we're so lucky.
你带我们来到了乐土
You've led us all to the Promised Land!
对不对 瑞克
Isn't that right, Rick?!
我们到了
Here we are!
我猜格伦和亚伯拉罕也很走运吧
I guess Glenn and Abraham were lucky, too?
再敢对我说类似的话
You say anything like that again to me,
我就打烂你的臭嘴 敲掉你的牙齿
I'll break your jaw, knock your teeth out.
明白吗
You understand?
说明白
Say yes.
明白
Yes.
你有枪
You had guns?
嗯
Uh-huh.
你之前为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me after I …
你看到我为拿到一把枪做了什么
You saw what I did to get one,
还没有子弹
that I need bullets.
我藏了有段时间了
I had them for a while.
因为我不信任瑞克
because I didn't trust Rick.
他管事让我担心
'Cause I was worried about him being in charge.
知道吗 你说的对
You know what? You were right.
这不是我们的命运
This doesn't have to be our life.
他们拿走了我们的床垫 大部分都拿走了
They took our mattresses … most of them.
那把步枪
That rifle.
是从他们哨站抢的
was one of theirs from the outpost.
单子上没有吧
They didn't have a list?
嗯
Unh-unh.
本可以藏更多的
Could've hidden more.
你藏了吗
Did you?
没有
No.
我们得到的一切 都是抗争得来的
Everything we have, we got from fighting.
我做出选择了
I made the choice.
我们人不够 这是人数问题
There aren't enough of us. It's about numbers.
还有山顶寨啊
There's the Hilltop.
他们人数依然更多
They'd still have the numbers.
我们遵守他们的规则 就能活下去
We play by their rules, and we get some kind of life.
怎么个活法
What kind of a life?
我曾有个朋友
You know, I had a friend.
我没提起过他
I don't talk about him.
他是我搭档
He was my partner.
灾变后 他把洛莉和卡尔带到了安全地
He got Lori and Carl to safety right after it all started.
我没法做到 我当时在医院
I couldn't. I was in the hospital.
我不知道发生了什么
I-I didn't know… what was happenin'.
我朋友
My friend…
他名字叫肖恩
His name was Shane.
他和洛莉
Well, him and Lori…
他们在一起了
they were together.
他们以为我死了
They thought I was dead.
我知道朱迪思不是我的
I know Judith isn't mine.
我知道
I know it.
我爱她
I love her.
她是我女儿
She's my daughter.
但她不是我骨肉
But she isn't mine.
我必须接受这点
I had to accept that.
我接受了
I did.
这样我就能保护她
So I could keep her alive.
我不死她就不会死
I'll die before she does,
希望那会是很久以后的事
and I hope that's a long time from now.
这样我可以
so I can…
抚养她长大 保护她 教她求生
raise her and protect her and teach her how to survive.
这就是我们现在的生存方式
This is how we live now.
我也必须接受这点
I had to accept that, too,
以保护所有人活下去
so I could keep everyone else alive.
人死不是你的错
It's not your fault when people die.
不总是 但是有时候是的
Not always, but sometimes … sometimes it is.
你必须接受
You have to accept this …
我们都要接受
all of us do …
不然行不通的
or it won't work.
我会试试
I'm gonna try.
给我做颗子弹
Make me a bullet.